Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Video and Film
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial loop, 11/2/98, 1998 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0389)
      Format: Beta
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial, 11/2/98, 1998 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0408)
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial loop, [1998] (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0387)
    - "Between Dreams and History" Installation Video Documentary, [1998] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0665)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Installation Video (dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0530)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Rivington Show A, [1998] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0613)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Rivington Show B, [1998] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0612)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Ludlow Show Master, 1998 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0611)
    - "Between Dreams and History: The Making of Shimon Attie's Public Art Projects" (dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0666)
    - Shimon Attie, "Between Dreams and History", BBC, Fall 1998 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0532)
    - Shimon Attie, "Between Dreams and History" (installation version, dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0534)
    - The Art Guys with Todd Oldham, "Suits: The Clothes Make the Man", 11/2/98, 1998 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0572)
    - The Art Guys, Haverford '98, 1998 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0610)
    - The Art Guys, [1998] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0578)
    - The Art Guys, CBS [Press], [1998] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0582)
    - Theresa Duncan, Jeremy Blake, "History of Glamour", [1998] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0676)
      Duration: [39 min.]
    - "F.R.E.D." Projections, Fall 1999 (shot by Roberto Guerra) (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0624)
      Format: MiniDV
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (art video looped) 5/18/99, 1999 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0301)
      Duration: [120 min.]
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (fashion video looped) 5/18/99, 1999 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0297)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (film video looped) 5/18/99, 1999 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0299)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged", [1999] (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0125)
    - Courtney Harmel, Brooklyn Library Projections, 11/6/99 (Tape 1), 1999 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0193)
    - Kyong Park, "Architecture of Resistance", 1999 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0691)
    - Standard and Poor, Carpet Rollers, Park Restaurant, 2/2/99, 1999 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0249)
    - The Art Guys, Fashion TV [Press], 1999 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0580)
    - The 59th Minute - Genevieve Cadieux, "Portrait", 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0279)
    - [Art in the Anchorage] - Granular Synthesis, "Noise Gate" (Prod. Footage), [2000] (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0187)
    - "Tibor in Orbit", Times Square, May-June, 2000 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0275)
    - Bus Tour, 9/27/00, 2000 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0291)
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap", 2000 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0454)
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap", Apr 27-30, 2000 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0448)
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap" (Demo), [2000] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0450)
    - "Leap", [2000] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0514)
    - "Leap", Dec[ember], [2000] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0452)
    - "Leap", Interviews, [2000] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0456)
    - Kyong Park, "Detroit: Making it Better For You", 12/2000 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0692)
    - The 59th Minute - "Tibor in Orbit", 4/4/00, 2000 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0351)
    - "Leap", "Tribute in Light", "Tap", "59th Minute" (show reel), [2000-2002] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0418)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Honest", June 2001 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0123)
      TRT: [44 min.]
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Massless Medium: Explorations Sensory Immersion", 2001 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0171)
    - Art in Anchorage - Leo Villareal, "Building as Display", "Megaparticle", "Cloud Chamber (sound)", "Strobe Display", "Chase Display", [2001] (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0133)
      Duration: [11 min.]
    - Barry McGee, "Mass Destruction", Shibuya-Ku, Tokyo (Filmed by Cheryl Dunn), 2001 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0684)
    - Bonnen, Phillips, "Shaded Bandwidth's Proposal", [2001] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0673)
      Duration: [7 min.]
    - Hans Haacke, May 12, 2001 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0245)
    - Mark Hansen, Ben Rubin, "Listening Post", 2001 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0661)
    - Mark Hansen, Ben Rubin, "Listening Post", 2001 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0662)
      Duration: [9 min.]
    - Music in the Anchorage - 6/21/01 (rough footage), 2001 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0646)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] - Porter Ricks, SND, 6/28 (#3), [2001] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0618)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] - Porter Ricks, Thomas Heckman, 6/28 (#4), [2001] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0620)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] 6/28 #3, [2001] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0622)
    - Noam Toran, "Object for Lonely Men", Blur, 2001 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0558)
    - Rachel Stevens, NAAMP Portfolio Presentation, 12/01, 2001 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0428)
    - The 59th Minute - Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, "ahistory", Oct 19-Nov 30, 2001 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0347)
    - The 59th Minute - Gary Hill, Michael Snow, Mary Lucier, "Fast Forward", 12/2/2001-1/27/02 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0369)
    - The 59th Minute - Marco Brambilla, "Superstar", Feb 28-Apr 15, 2001 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0353)
    - The 59th Minute - Marco Brambilla, "Superstar"; Fischli and Weiss, "Cat Drinking Milk"; William Kentridge, "Shadow", 2001 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0257)
    - The 59th Minute - Michael Snow, "Fridge", 2001 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0478)
    - The 59th Minute - Fischli and Weiss, "Cat Drinking Milk"; William Kentridge, "Shadows"; Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, "ahistory"; Jeff Gibson, "Viralysis"; Gary Hill, "Liminal Object"; Mary Lucier, "Monarch"; Michael Snow, "Fridge"; Genevieve Cadieux, "Portrait", [2001] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0480)
    - Vik Muniz, "What's The Big Idea" [EGG, The Arts Show], [2001] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0678)
    - "Out of the Ashes", "Towers of Light", Dateline, 10/21/01 [Press], 2001 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0492)
    - "Out of the Ashes", Dateline, 10/21/01 [Press], 2001 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0287)
    - Memorials, CBS Evening News, 12/11/01 [Press], 2001 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0281)
    - "Tribute in Light" press conference, 3/6/02 (part 1 of 2) [Press], 2002 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0424)
    - "Tribute in Light", Anne Pasternak, Pure Oxygen, 3/12/02 [Press], 2002 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0550)
    - "Tribute in Light", Nippon Television, Tokyo, 3/9/02 [Press], 2002 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0422)
    - "Tribute in Light", Nippon Television, Tokyo, 3/9/02 [Press], 2002 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0546)
    - "Tribute in Light", Press Conference (tape 2 of 2) [Press], 2002 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0548)
    - "Tribute in Light", Pure Oxygen, 4/10/02 (Segment B) [Press], 2002 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0426)
    - "Tribute in Light", CNN, Towers of Light [Press], [2002] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0544)
    - "Tribute in Light", Illumina TV, ArtsWorld [Press], [2002] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0494)
    - "Tribute in Light", NY One [Press], [2002] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0496)
    - "Tribute in Light", Towers of Light, Proun Space Studio, [2002] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0498)
    - Therese Cafaro, Jayson Haedrich, "Tribute: A Documentary", [2002] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0672)
      Duration: [27 min.]
    - Therese Cafaro, Jayson Haedrich, "Tribute: A Documentary", [2002] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0420)
    - Everton Sylvester, Skylight Gallery, 9/5/02 (Tape 2), 2002 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0153)
    - Everton Sylvester, Skylight Gallery, 9/5/02 (Tape 4), 2002 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0165)
    - Everton Sylvester, 9/5/02 (tape 1), 2002 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0640)
    - Everton Sylvester, 9/5/02 (tape 3), 2002 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0630)
    - Gabri SI High School 9/13/02 (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0614)
    - Gabri SI High School, 9/13/02 (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0648)
    - Holiday Light Show - Grand Central Project, Comp Reel, [2002] (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0285)
    - James Buckhouse, Holly Brubach, "Tap" - Tech TV (30 second spot), 6/12/2002 [Press] (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0283)
    - "Sonic Garden", NY Tonight [Press], [2002] (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0295)
    - Stephanie Simon, "Poster Project", 2/02, 2002 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0267)
    - The Kitchen and Creative Time - DHH Winless NY, 4/23/02, 2002 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0175)
      Duration: [56 min.]
    - Toshi, 8/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0632)
    - Toshi, 8/28/02 (2 of 2), 2002 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0616)
    - William Wegman - [The 59th Minute] Fox Good Day Live, 11/18/02 [Press], 2002 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0373)
    - Adelle Lutz, "The Peace Piece", [2003]; 179.0604 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0604, E-records fales_mss179)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Original format: VHS, Duration: 00:04:00
    - Artist Roundtable (final group discussion), 8/5/03, 2003 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0135)
    - Artist Roundtable (Vardit's Group), 8/5/03, 2003 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0149)
    - Artists Roundtable, Vardit, [2003] (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0502)
    - Artist Roundtable, Carol's Group, 8/5/03, 2003 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0638)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Gunpowder", drawings at Grucci, 8/7/03, 2003 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0634)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Light Cycle", 2003 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0273)
    - [Cai Guo-Qiang], "Light Cycle", "Aerial", [2003] (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0189)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Light Cycle", [2003] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0636)
    - Focus Group, 3/24/03 (1 of 2), 2003 (Box not specified, Folder ID: 179.0642)
    - Focus Group, 3/24/03 (2 of 2), 2003 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0644)
    - The 59th Minute - Carlos Amorales, "The Forest", 2003 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0669)
    - The 59th Minute - William Wegman, "Dog Duet", 2003 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0401)
    - The 59th Minute - Thomas Struth, 2003 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0385)
    - [The 59th Minute] - Thomas Struth, "Video Portraits": Kim Heirston, Thomas Gutt, Anne Grefe, Rafael Hartmann, [2003] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0606)
    - Thomas Struth Exhibit, German television, 2/4/03 [Press], 2003 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0361)
    - "Worst Possible Illusion: The Curiosity Cabinet of Vik Muniz", [2003] (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0671)
      Duration: [5 min.]
    - CBS Sunday Morning, "Freedom of Expression", 7/4/04 [Press], 2004 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0293)
    - Freedom of Expression [Monument], 11/04, 2004 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0488)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For New York City" (1), 2004 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0584)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For New York City" (2), 2004 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0592)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For The City" (raw footage), [2004] (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0586)
    - "For New York City", '04, Xenon Projections at Bethesda Fountain, Central Park, 10/2704 (tape 4), 2004 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0590)
    - O and A [Sam Auinger and Bruce Odland], "Blue Moon", Stephanie Simon 5/04 [Press], 2004 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0470)
    - The 59th Minute - "Dream Sequence", "Dwelling", "Mousetrap", 1/18/04, 2004 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0307)
    - The 59th Minute - Carlos Amorales, "The Forest", 10/28/04, 2004 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0309)
    - The 59th Minute - Gunther Selichar, [2004] (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0247)
    - The 59th Minute - Hiraki Sawa, "Dwelling"; Janaina Tschape, "Dream Sequence", Jan 21-May 16, 2004 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0377)
    - The 59th Minute - Hiraki Sawa, "Dwelling"; Janaina Tschape, "Dream Sequence", Jan 21-May 16, 2004 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0414)
    - The 59th Minute - [Carlos] Amorales, Televisa New York, [2004-2005] (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0482)
    - Anne Pasternak, Stephanie Simon, 2/05 [Press], 2005 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0269)
    - Dreamland Artist Club - Stephanie Simon, 2005 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0129)
    - Jenny Holzer, Bobst Library, NYU, 11/16/05, 2005 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0588)
    - Jenny Holzer, Political Art (edit), Reuters, Fall 2005 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0594)
    - Song Dong, "Evaporating Art", Reuters, 2005 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0371)
    - "Life During Wartime", 6/12/?, Undated (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0686)
    - "Living With AIDS: Seize Control of the FDA", Undated (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0522)
    - # 4, 6/28, Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0145)
    - [unidentified], Undated (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0650)
    - [unidentified], Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0163)
    - [unidentified], Undated (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0554)
    - 1st Tape "R", Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0199)
    - Ange Leccia, Undated (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0359)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 1), Undated (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0329)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 2, Kay Lynn), Undated (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0343)
    - Art on the Beach (tape 3, Kay Lynn), Undated (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0355)
      Format: 3/4"
    - Art on the Beach (tape 5), Undated (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0375)
    - Bill Shannon, Axis Dance and Solo, Undated (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0367)
    - Bravo, "Unfinished Stories" (presentation tape), Undated (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0667)
      Duration: [2 min.]
    - Brooklyn Library, Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0183)
    - Burlesque Video, 2 Versions, Undated (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0432)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Pyrotechnic Projects", Undated (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0664)
    - Dreamland Artist Club, Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0131)
    - Emergency Broadcast Network, Video Press Kit, Undated (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0680)
    - Fair and Balanced News/ Freedom, Undated (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0524)
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0137)
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0197)
    - Grand Central Installation, Undated (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0626)
    - Granular Synthesis, Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0173)
    - Jim Campbell, "Untitled (Agora)", Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0205)
    - Joan Giummo, "Fire Sign", Undated (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0688)
    - Kathy Brew, Roberto Guerra, DNAID, Undated (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0271)
    - Marjetica Potrc, "Borders" (Tape 1), Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0179)
    - Marjetica Potrc, "Borders" (tape 2, beginning of general discussion), Undated (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0628)
    - Susan Cianciolo, "Diadel", Undated (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0181)
    - Thomas Harris, "AIDs and Art", The Eleventh Hour #266, WNET Thirteen, Undated (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0685)
    - William Kentridge, Undated (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0259)
    - Zhang Huan, Undated; 179.0127 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0127, E-records fales_mss179)
      Original format: MiniDV, Duration: 50 min.
  - Subseries C: Film
    - Art on the Beach, Undated (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0698)
      Format: Super 8 film
  - Subseries D: Video Recordings - Submasters - CLOSED
    Conditions Governing Access
    CLOSED
    - ID: 179.0686 - 179.0773, undated (Box PM 8)
      Scope and Contents
      Contains materials numbered 179.0686, 179.0689, 179.0692, 179.0695, 179.0698, 179.0701, 179.0704, 179.0707, 179.0710, 179.0713, 179.0716, 179.0719, 179.0722, 179.0725, 179.0728, 179.0731, 179.0734, 179.0737, 179.0740, 179.0743, 179.0746, 179.0749, 179.0752, 179.0755, 179.0758, 179.0761, 179.0764, 179.0767, 179.0770, 179.0773
    - Masstransiscope by Bill Brand 1980, 2008 (Box PM 10, Case 179.0775)
  - Subseries E: Video Recordings - Preservation Masters - CLOSED
    - ID: 179.0685 - 179.0724 (Box PM 49)
    - ID: 179.0727 - 179.0766 (Box PM 50)
    - ID: 179.0679, 179.0772 (Box PM 51)
- Series VI: Audio
  This series includes audio recordings from the Creative Time Archive. Titles are arranged chronologically by year. Compilation tapes are arranged chronologically by first year represented on tape. Material includes performances, news broadcasts, speeches, source material, and other miscellaneous recordings. Researcher access is limited to Subseries A – Audio Recordings – Access Copies.
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings - Access Copies
    - Art on the Beach, 1985 (Case 179.0075)
      Format: CD-R
      Original Original Format: Audio cassette
    - Art on the Beach - NPR, 9/3/85 [Press], 1985 (Case 179.0108)
      Original Format: Audio cassette
    - Art on the Beach - side a: Last Day Concert; side b: 9/14/85 [part 1], 1985 (Case 179.0120)
    - Art on the Beach - side a: Last Day Concert; side b: 9/14/85 [part 2], 1985 (Case 179.0121)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Guerrilla Girls, 6/16/87, 1987 (Case 179.0086)
    - Lenny Pickett with the Borneo Horns, [1987] (Case 179.0044)
    - Live Recordings from [1987-]1988 (for NEA Music Program FY90) (Case 179.0088)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Joan Jonas Soundtrack, [1988] (Case 179.0079)
    - Recordings from 1988-1991 (for NEA Music Program FY92) (Case 179.0116)
    - "Video/Musica", Nov 1989 [part 1] (Case 179.0063)
    - "Video/Musica", Nov 1989 [part 2] (Case 179.0064)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Christiane Vaillancourt, NPR, July 1989 [Press] (Case 179.0040)
    - Art in the Anchorage - NPR Broadcast, 7/27/89 [Press], 1989 (Case 179.0048)
    - Bob Holman Interview, "Poets in the Bars", NOMMO Radio, 4/11/89, 1989 (Case 179.0094)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Arthur Russell, 9/6/91, 1991 (Case 179.0028)
      Original Format: DAT cassette
    - Art in the Anchorage - Bosho, 9/7/91, 1991 (Case 179.0026)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Guy Yarden, 9/7/91, 1991 (Case 179.0030)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Hugo Largo, 9/5/91, 1991 (Case 179.0032)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Linda Fisher, 9/05/91, 1991 (Case 179.0024)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Linda Fisher, 9/5/91, 1991 (Case 179.0110)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Manhattan Marimba Quartet, 1991 (Case 179.0058)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Manhattan Marimba Quartet, 9/6/91, 1991 (Case 179.0056)
    - Jerri Allyn, "Angels Have Been Sent To Me" [side a: Eng; side b: Spa] [part 1], 1991 (Case 179.0103)
    - Jerri Allyn, "Angels Have Been Sent To Me" [side a: Eng; side b: Spa] [part 2], 1991 (Case 179.0104)
    - Music Samples, Spring 1991 [part 1] (Case 179.0068)
    - Music Samples, Spring 1991 [part 2] (Case 179.0069)
    - Selections for NEA Review, 1991 (Case 179.0052)
    - John Pietro, compilation tape, 1992 (Case 179.0042)
    - Masterpieces Without The Director, Milk Carton Project, WBAI, 2/8/92 [Press], 1992 (Case 179.0054)
      Duration: [59 min.]
    - Norman Salant, "Saxophone Stories", 10/92, 1992 (Case 179.0066)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - NPR, 7/8/93 [Press], 1993 (Case 179.0106)
    - Board Meeting, 9/29/93 [part 1], 1993 (Case 179.0083)
    - Board Meeting, 9/29/93 [part 2], 1993 (Case 179.0084)
    - Norman Salant, "sax/on", "After Ours" [part 1], 1994 (Case 179.0060)
    - Norman Salant, "sax/on", "After ours" [part 2], 1994 (Case 179.0061)
    - Julia Meltzer, Amanda Ramos, "Chatlandia, 3 Conversations", [1995] (Case 179.0118)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Ben Neill, July 27 [part 1], [1996] (Case 179.0034)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Ben Neill, July 27 [part 2], [1996] (Case 179.0035)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Vernon Reid, July 27 [part 1], [1996] (Case 179.0037)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Vernon Reid, July 27 [part 2], [1996] (Case 179.0038)
    - Paco Cao, [1996] (Case 179.0010)
      Original Format: Microcassette
    - Phil Kline, "Winter Music", 12/96, 1996 (Case 179.0073)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Adrianne Wortzel proposal, 2/25/97, 1997 (Case 179.0071)
    - Guillermo Gomez-Pena, "El Mexterminator", 1997 (Case 179.0112)
    - "El Mexterminator", WBAI Voices Against the Wall, 6/5/98 [Press] [part 1], 1998 (Case 179.0100)
    - "El Mexterminator", WBAI Voices Against the Wall, 6/5/98 [Press] [part 2], 1998 (Case 179.0101)
    - Karen Finley, "A Message from…", 1-900-ALL-KAREN, 2/16/98, 1998 (Case 179.0090)
    - Shimon Attie, "Tribute to Joe Papp", 11/1/98, 1998 (Case 179.0081)
    - CT Interview - Anne Pasternak, 10/09/01, "On WTC response", 2001 (Case 179.0018)
    - CT Interview - Anne Pasternak, 12/03/01, "General", 2001 (Case 179.0020)
    - CT Interview - Carol Stakenas, 10/26/01, 2001 (Case 179.0012)
      Duration: [55 min.]
    - CT Interview - Elizabeth Iarrappino, 11/9/01, 2001 (Case 179.0002)
    - CT Interview - Kelly Evans, 11/14/01, 2001 (Case 179.0008)
    - CT Interview - Kevin [McHugh], 11/09/01, 2001 (Case 179.0022)
    - CT Interview - Prof. Harriet Senie, 11/29/01, 2001 (Case 179.0006)
    - CT Interview - Rachel Stevens, 11/12/01, 2001 (Case 179.0014)
    - CT Interview - Sarah Bacon, 11/02/01, 2001 (Case 179.0016)
      Duration: [40 min.]
    - Memorial Discussion, 3/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002 (Case 179.0097)
    - Memorial Meeting, NYU, 3/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002 (Case 179.0098)
    - Anita Contini Interview, Artists' Space, Christian Science Monitor (Cut #4), Undated (Case 179.0092)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Closing Party, Tape #1, Undated (Case 179.0077)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Closing Party, Tape #2, Undated (Case 179.0050)
    - Calvin Trillin, Undated (Case 179.0114)
    - Karen Tape, Undated (Case 179.0004)
    - NEA Music Tape Copy, Undated (Case 179.0046)
  - Subseries B: Audio Recordings - Originals
    - Ann Wilson, "Butler's Lives of the Saints", Jan 1978 (Box 32, Reel 179.0699, E-records fales_mss179, E-records 179.0699)
      1/4" Open Reel Audio, 87 min.
    - Art on the Beach, 1985 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0074)
      Format: Audio cassette
    - Art on the Beach - NPR, 9/3/85 [Press], 1985 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0107)
    - Art on the Beach - side a: Last Day Concert; side b: 9/14/85, 1985 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0119)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Guerrilla Girls, 6/16/87, 1987 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0085)
    - Lenny Pickett with the Borneo Horns, [1987] (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0043)
    - Live Recordings from [1987-]1988 (for NEA Music Program FY90) (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0087)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Joan Jonas Soundtrack, [1988] (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0078)
    - Recordings from 1988-1991 (for NEA Music Program FY92) (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0115)
    - "Video/Musica", Nov 1989 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0062)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Christiane Vaillancourt, NPR, July 1989 [Press] (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0039)
    - Art in the Anchorage - NPR Broadcast, 7/27/89 [Press], 1989 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0047)
    - Bob Holman Interview, "Poets in the Bars", NOMMO Radio, 4/11/89, 1989 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0093)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Arthur Russell, 9/6/91, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0027)
      Format: DAT cassette
    - Art in the Anchorage - Bosho, 9/7/91, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0025)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Guy Yarden, 9/7/91, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0029)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Hugo Largo, 9/5/91, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0031)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Linda Fisher, 9/05/91, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0023)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Linda Fisher, 9/5/91, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0109)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Manhattan Marimba Quartet, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0057)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Manhattan Marimba Quartet, 9/6/91, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0055)
    - Jerri Allyn, "Angels Have Been Sent To Me" [side a: Eng; side b: Spa], 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0102)
    - Music Samples, Spring 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0067)
    - Selections for NEA Review, 1991 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0051)
    - John Pietro, compilation tape, 1992 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0041)
    - Masterpieces Without The Director, Milk Carton Project, WBAI, 2/8/92 [Press], 1992 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0053)
    - Norman Salant, "Saxophone Stories", 10/92, 1992 (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0065)